grandcanyon.com 2013-10-06

# GrandCanyon.com Privacy Policy

GrandCanyon.com is concerned about your right to privacy. When you visit the GrandCanyon.com website, you can be assured that any information you provide to us will be handled carefully. We will never sell or rent your information to any third party. Your credit card information, date of birth, physical address, e-mail address, and phone number(s) will not be shared with any third parties except:

  * Under legal subpoena
  * To verify billing information with the Customer's financial institution
  * For credit card fraud detection
  * To complete a transaction when a Customer purchases service from a travel service provider (i.e. hotel, show, ground tour, etc.) that is accessible through GrandCanyon.com.

This site contains links to other sites. GrandCanyon.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Our website utilizes cookies. This enables our system to recognize your browser and keep track of your reservation information. We also utilize cookies to track the effectiveness of our online advertising. The information carried by the cookies;

  * Contains no individually identifiable data
  * Will be treated as confidential by GrandCanyon.com
  * Will only be used to make informed decisions regard the performance of our online advertising initiatives.

In short, these efforts help us to provide you, our customer, with the best value on all of our spectacular air and ground tours.

GrandCanyon.com (grandcanyon.com) reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. In the event that we make a material change to our policy we will post a notice of the change on this page.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site please contact:

GrandCanyon.com, Inc.  
PO Box 1117  
Page, AZ 86040

info@grandcanyon.com
